Guide to the Rice University KTRU Radio records, 1962-2018 UA 011
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series I: Audio recordings, 1968-2007, 59004
  - Sub-Series: 1975/1976, 59187
    - Backstage Interview - Hall & Oates, Spring 1976; wrc06530; 59186 (Box 5)
      Contents include: On "Backstage Interview," Bruce Kessler interviews Daryl Hall and John Oates. The duo discusses their musical backgrounds, their history together, their early albums, work with Todd Rundgren on War Babies, genre change with War Babies, and working on new album. Speakers: Daryl Hall, John Oates, Bruce Kessler
    - News Master 2, Spring 1976; wrc06531; 59218 (Box 5)
      Contents include: (00:01) NBC correspondents at Rice; (01:26) Charles Daniels controversy; (02:21) Add/drop courses; (02:57) Recruiting; (03:58) Applications for job; (04:24) Thresher salary increases; (05:34) Opinions on Thresher, salary increase; (08:48) Stan Barber is a nitwit; (09:09) Charles Daniels controversy; (10:32) Hiring of David Hunt, Director of Financial Aid; (12:28) Acoustics installation in Willy's Pub, funding new ideas; (15:37) Football coach search; (17:31) Thresher salary increase vote; (18:01) Homer Rice to be offered coaching job; (19:50) Homer Rice news conference; (25:05) Ford Administration meetings with Houston; (26:54) Thresher salary increase vote failed, Student Association meeting; (27:50) Homer Rice press conference; (28:58) Stan Barber interview with Joyce Rubash on food quality; (34:11) Rice Owls track Olympic trials, Jeff Wells; (36:38) Valhalla crime incident; (38:39) Department of Biology, curriculum additions, labs; (40:11) Memorial Park oil wells; (43:13) Universities Space Research Association institutes; (45:04) Accounting profession. Speakers: Stan Barber, Charles Daniels, Lee Hochberg, Norman Hackerman, Homer Rice, James Castaneda, Dana Blankenhorn, Joyce Rubash, Jeff Wells, C.B. Bernick
    - News Master 3, Spring 1976; wrc06532; 59220 (Box 5)
      Contents include: (00:01) University evaluation day, the role of the university; (02:04) Zip code realignment; (03:14) Survey of issue; (03:48) Gazilcher at Sid Richardson College; (04:51) Financial aid; (05:35) Student Association election candidates; (06:51) "From the Perspective of Professionals" panel; (10:08) Student opinions on convocation; (13:36) University standing committees; (15:37) Stephen Klineberg at convocation; (17:02) Workshop on introductory courses; (18:10) Course summary; (19:39) Campanile publishing issue; (20:35) Campanile dispersal; (20:49) Athlete training; (21:01) Rice Alternative Basketball Team challenges Rice Owls basketball team; (22:11) Student Association elections; (22:48) Farmer's Market; (23:43) Meal plans; (26:45) Candidate financial statements; (27:30) Basketball player; (27:43) Rice Owls basketball game play-by-play; (30:55) University of Texas underrated team; (31:39) Willy's Pub changes; (34:34) President's Honor Roll; (36:41) Homer Rice on student involvement in athletic program; (38:39) MOB at Mardi Gras in New Orleans; (39:57) Summer school course summaries; (43:41) Rice Owls baseball review; (44:26) St. Patrick's Day dance; (45:04) Student Association elections; (45:33) Student Association meeting review. Speakers: Larry Fossi, Stephen Klineberg, Craig Ball, James Morehead, Stan Barber, Homer Rice, Jim Cobb, Bill Wade
    - News Master 4, Spring 1976; wrc06533; 59222 (Box 5)
      Contents include: Spring 1976 news master (00:01) Committee on the Convocation; (01:57) Mail delivery; (02:55) Nature class at arboretum; (05:09) Republican primary; (05:24) New Hanszen College commons; (06:08) Athletics press conference, athletes admissions, facilities, recruiting; (09:01) Student Association meeting review, elections; (11:49) Norman Hackerman on recruiting; (12:28) Room and board increases; (14:06) Committee anxious; (15:10) Gilbert Cuthbertson on primaries and John Connally, Will Rice College room jack; (26:18) Birds on campus, tree pruning; (29:18) Female College Master at a male college; (32:22) The role of the master; (34:45) Student Association election controversy; (35:04) Oil drilling in Memorial Park; (36:08) University of Texas Student Association president joke candidate. Speakers: Roy Bellar, Homer Rice, Norman Hackerman, Gilbert Cuthbertson, Constantine Armeniades, Katherine Tsanoff Brown
    - News Master 5, Spring 1976; wrc06534; 59217 (Box 5)
      Contents include: (00:01) Gilbert Cuthbertson; (00:46) Memorial Park oil drilling; (02:08) "We Can Do It" workshop; (04:32) Student Association election controversy; (05:09) Summer chillers, closing down buildings, Resident Associates; (07:49) Hasnzen College B and P coffeehouse; (09:10) Houston bond election; (10:09) Memorial Park oil drilling; (11:12) Miller Theater Spring festival; (13:48) Rice Media Center presents King Vidor; Government Policy in the Arts panel; Art in American in the 1930s and Now; (20:04) Masters Committee finalizing new Masters for Sid Richardson and Will Rice College; (21:09) Ron Paul special election; (24:04) River Oaks World Championship of Tennis tournament; (27:54) Rice Owls baseball game preview; (29:01) William Martin and Constantine Armeniades named Masters; (29:53) Memorial Park oil drilling. Speakers: Stan Barber, Norman Hackerman, Barbie Siever, Tom Moe, Jim Cobb
    - News Master 6, Spring 1976; wrc06535; 59216 (Box 5)
      Contents include: (00:01) Will Rice College student opinion of Constantine Armeniades; (01:55) River Oaks World Championship of Tennis tournament; (04:03) Admissions; (04:44) F. Barry Dunning wins Sloan Fellowship for Basic Research; (05:48) Energy speaker; (06:20) Robert R. Sterling appointed Dean of Jones Business School; (10:18) Critique of government funded art, foreign aid; (11:58) Severe weather tips; (14:21) Mailings; (14:33) Ronald Reagan not electable; (15:23) Alumni on the Board of Trustees; (15:54) I-610 jackknife; (16:38) Scientific research funding slowing; (17:25) Hare and the Hound race; (18:02) Tennesse primary results; (19:21) Honor Council violation. Speakers: Barbie Siever, James Castaneda, Stan Barber, Robert Sterling, Tom Moe, Norman Hackerman, Jim Cobb
    - Backstage Interview - Cecilio and Kapono, 1976-05-02; wrc07925 (Box 5)
      Contents include: On "Backstage Interview," Bruce Kessler talks to Cecilio and Kapono about their acoustic style, songwriting, touring, new music, and working together. Speakers: Henry Kapono Ka'aihue, Cecilio David Rodriguez, Bruce Kessler
    - Backstage Interview - The Tubes, 1976-05-19; wrc07947 (Box 5)
      Contents include: On "Backstage Interview," Bruce Kessler talks Fee Waybill of The Tubes about integrating visuals to music, difficulties recording "The Tubes," easier to record "Young and Rich," live shows, stage crew, character inspirations, new charcters, album notes, and comparisons to KISS. Speakers: Bruce Kessler, Fee Waybill
    - Station IDs, 1976-1983; wrc08003 (Box 5)
      Contents include: (00:01) Gary Wright; (00:13) Iggy Pop; (00:25) Graham Parker; (00:34) Boz Scaggs; (00:44) Eric Bloom; (00:59) Fee Waybill; (01:12) Stevie Nicks; (01:31) Mick Fleetwood; (01:44) Janis Ian; (01:53) Frank Zappa; (02:08) Rick Wakeman; (02:15) Jon Anderson; (02:22) Rick Nielsen; (02:56) Cheap Trick; (03:22) Hall and Oates; (03:32) Brad Delp; (03:46) Robert Klein; (04:19) Jan Hammer; (04:32) Joan Jett and Lee Crystal; (04:49) Joe "King" Carrasco; (05:24) Phil Woods; (05:38) Roger McGuinn; (05:54) Walter Cronkite; (06:07) Charlotte Caffey and Kathy Valentine; (06:50) Laurie Anderson; (08:01) Andy McCluskey; (08:09) Dr. Rockit and the Sisters of Mercy; (09:17) Bill Nolan; (09:32) Brian Setzer; (09:43) Brian O'Neill; (09:55) Lee Rocker; (10:10) Slim Jim Phantom; (10:42) The Bangles; (11:13) Dee Dee Ramone; (11:39) Joey Ramone; (12:09) Johnny Ramone; (12:22) Marc Moreland; (13:02) Lene Lovich; (13:14) King Sunny Adé; (14:10) Fred Schneider and Keith Strickland. Speakers: Gary Wright, Iggy Pop, Graham Parker, Boz Scaggs, Eric Bloom, Fee Waybill, Stevie Nicks, Mick Fleetwood, Janis Ian, Frank Zappa, Rick Wakeman, Jon Anderson, Rick Nielsen, Daryl Hall, John Oates, Brad Delp, Robert Klein, Jan Hammer, Joan Jett, Lee Crystal, Joe "King" Currasco, Phil Woods, Roger McGuinn, Walter Cronkite, Charlotte Caffey, Kathy Valentin, Laurie Anderson, Andy McCluskey, Rock Romano, Bill Nolan, Brian Setzer, Brian O'Neill, Lee Rocker, Slim Jim Phantom, Dee Dee Ramone, Joey Ramone, Johnny Ramone, Marc Moreland, Lene Lovich, King Sunny Adé, Fred Schneider, Keith Strickland
  - Sub-Series: 1976/1977, 59207
    - Democratic National Convention report, 1976-07-17; wrc06549; 59192 (Box 5)
      Contents include: Larry Fossi reports on the upcoming selection of Jimmy Carter as the democratic presidential candidate, Rep. Barbara Jordan's speech, and speculation on Carter's vice presidential selection. We deleted radio music at the beginning of the recording. Speakers: Larry Fossi, Stan Barber
    - Alan Steelman interview, 1976-09-15; wrc06550; 59188 (Box 5)
      Contents include: Stan Barber interviews State Congressman Alan Steelman on the topics of his voting record, the Trinity project, reviewing federal laws at the state level, abortion, retirement age, and his opponent Sen. Lloyd Bentsen. Speakers: Stan Barber, Alan Steelman
    - Rice Thoughts - Co-ed Colleges, 1976-09-21; wrc06551; 59232 (Box 5)
      Contents include: Stan Barber interviews students on their views on co-ed colleges for the show Rice Thoughts. Students discuss the programs successes. As for the merits of the single sex college, some students think co-ed colleges make men more docile, lack privacy, and cause co-ed college alienation. We fixed a reversed audio issue, but ended up deleting the material, since it was only outtakes. Speaker: Stan Barber
    - News Master, 1976-09; wrc06552; 59215 (Box 5)
      Contents include: (00:01) Rice Owls football vs. Utah preview; (02:21) Pets on campus; (02:59) Homer Rice on Rice Owls football vs. Utah preview; (03:45) Jimmy Carter campaign, visit to Houston; (09:25) Gentle Art of Sports Betting, college sports; (10:58) Stop smoking course. Speaker: Dana Blankenhorn
    - Jimmy Carter interview and campaigning, 1976-09-24; wrc07930 (Box 5)
      Contents include: Presidential candidate Jimmy Carter speaks to reporters after getting off of his airplane. He discusses the previous night's debate, issues with Pres. Gerald Ford, the Playboy article, and his religion. Then, there is a political rally in which Mayor Fred Hofheinz, Senator Lloyd Bentsen, Governor Dolph Briscoe, and Jimmy Carter speak. KTRU reporters also speak with protest groups at the rally. We deleted dead air throughout the recording. Speakers: Jimmy Carter, Fred Hofheinz, Lloyd Bentsen, Dolph Briscoe
    - St. Elmo's Fire interview and music, 1976-09-26; wrc06553; 59200 (Box 5)
      Contents include: St. Elmo's Fire playing live at KTRU. During the interview portions, the band discusses their first performance, their music recordings, Caliban with the Houston Ballet, changing their name from Wheatfield to St. Elmo's Fire, the steps to recording an album, choosing a record company, and the story behind some of their songs. They also create stations IDs. This is a poor recording. Speakers: Ezra Idlet, Connie Mims, Craig Calvert, Damian Hevia, Keith Grimwood
    - Arbuckle Flat - Stephen Jarrard, 1976-10-05; wrc06554; 59239 (Box 5)
      Contents include: Stephen Jarrard playing live on the "Arbuckle Flat" radio program. It is a poor recording. Speakers: Stephen Jarrard, Trip Doss
    - Arbuckle Flat - Bill Cade, 1976-10-19; wrc06555; 59233 (Box 5)
      Contents include: Bill Cade on the "Arbuckle Flat" radio program. It starts with a quick conversation with Bill Cade and his band, and then moves onto Cade playing live in the studio. Speakers: Bill Cade, Trip Doss
    - Backstage Interview - Boston, 1976-10-23; wrc07933 (Box 5)
      Contents include: On "Backstage Interview," Bruce Kessler talks to members of the band Boston about their tour, production values, Scholz's basement studio, popular songs, regional popularity, album cover, musical influences, sound effects, lyrics, and The Beatles. Speakers: Tom Scholz, Sib Hashian, Barry Goudreau, Brad Delp, Fran Sheehan
    - So Now You Can Vote - Bob Gammage, 1976-10-28; wrc06556; 59208 (Box 5)
      Contents include: Democratic candidate for the U.S. House of Representatives Bob Gammage discusses Rep. Ron Paul and his libertarian values, Paul's voting record, National Science Foundation grant funding, gun control, and oil and gas. Speakers: Bob Gammage, Ron Paul
    - Outtakes, 1976-10-29; wrc06557; 59213 (Box 5)
      Contents include: (00:01) Pres. Gerald Ford and Jimmy Carter reports; (07:29) Political and international news, DJ practicing; (10:07) Music; (11:20) "Yellow Submarine" broadcast sign-off; (12:43) Great Flood anniversary; (16:13) "Yellow Submarine" broadcast sign-off; (17:42) Not Necessarily True News with fake commercials. Speakers: Gerald Ford, Jimmy Carter, Lee Hochberg, David Zumwalt
    - 1976 Election Coverage, part 1, 1976-11-02; wrc06558_01; 59193 (Box 6)
      Contents include: Reporting on the 1976 national and local elections. Various guests, KTRU DJs, and others discuss the incoming election results. Speakers: Gilbert Cuthbertson, Joel Laser, David Butler, Ray Hutchinson, Patti Bellis, Stan Barber, Ken Meyer, Dana Blankenhon, John Connally, Bob Gammage, Scott Hochberg, Ron Paul, Lloyd Bentsen, Bill Hobby, Hubert Holmes
    - 1976 Election Coverage, part 2, 1976-11-02; wrc06558_02; 59198 (Box 6)
      Contents include: Reporting on the 1976 national and local elections. Various guests, KTRU DJs, and others discuss the incoming election results. Speakers: Lee Hochberg, David Butler, Tom Moe, Stan Barber, Bob Gammage, Hubert Holmes, Ray Hutchinson
    - Up in the Air - Recycling, 1976-11-04; wrc06560; 59223 (Box 6)
      Contents include: Dr. Mike Kessick, Environmental Engineering, Noel Shenoi, Rice Recycling Center, Jerry Akers of the Sierra Club, and Duane Marks discuss recycling and environmental efforts on campus, in Houston, and nationally. They also discuss pollution in Houston. Towards the end of the recording, the recording speed increases causing the voices to sound strange and eventually unrecognizable. We fixed this issue, but there is some residual distortion. Speakers: Mike Kessick, Noel Shenoi, Jerry Akers, Duane Marks
    - Al Stewart - in concert - Tower Theatre (2 CDs), 1976-11-07; wrc06561; 59199 (Box 6)
      Contents include: Al Stewart playing live in Philadelphia at the Tower Theatre via radio station WMMR. At 01:23:41, Frankie Vee and the Village Boys live in Baker Commons on 1976-10-15. The recording is poor. The second recording was probably left over from a previous recorded broadcast. Speakers: Al Stewart, Frankie Vee and the Village Boys
    - Arbuckle Flat - Montrose Marching Band, 1976-11-08; wrc06562; 59241 (Box 6)
      Contents include: Montrose Marching Band playing live on the "Arbuckle Flat" radio program. We deleted radio music at the end of this recording. Speakers: Montrose Marching Band, Trip Doss
    - Arbuckle Flat - John Grimaudo, 1976-11-16; wrc06564; 59227 (Box 6)
      Contents include: John Grimaudo playing live on the "Arbuckle Flat" radio program. Speakers: John Grimaudo, Trip Doss
    - Up in the Air - Fred Hofhienz, 1976-11-18; wrc06565; 59224 (Box 6)
      Contents include: Stan Barber interviews Houston Mayor Fred Hofheinz. They discuss the Southwestern Bell Telephone Co., Houston water quality, enforcing vehicle laws, elections, the June 15, 1976 flood, the recent national election, drunk driving, and park. Speakers: Stan Barber, Fred Hofheinz
    - Arbuckle Flat - Reb Smith, 1976-11-23; wrc06566; 59242 (Box 6)
      Contents include: Reb Smith playing live on the "Arbuckle Flat" radio program. Speakers: Reb Smith, Trip Doss
    - Up in the Air - Bob Polk, 1976-11-24; wrc06563; 59225 (Box 6)
      Contents include: An interview with Rice Owls Basketball Coach Bob Polk. He discusses Rice's poor SWC basketball rankings, Coach Eddie Sutton, recruitment, the upcoming line-up, scholarships, and low student attendance at games. At times, the audio quality is poor. Speakers: Bob Polk, Dana Blankenhorn
    - Football season review, 1976-11-27; wrc06567; 59226 (Box 6)
      Contents include: (00:01) Director of Athletics and Football Coach Homer Rice on the 1976 season and the problems that plagued it, like player injuries; (05:26) Interview with quarterback Tommy Kramer about his college career and the NFL draft; (12:04) Interview with Doug Cunningham and Doug Houser about the football season; (24:07) Homer Rice continues to speak on wanting to improve the women's sports program, as well as football; (27:32) Interview with Wes Hansen, Steve Pasterchick, Doug Loafman, Don Rutledge, and Bobby Scheihing on the football season. Audio quality is poor at times. Speakers: Homer Rice, Tommy Kramer, Doug Cunningham, Dave Houser, Wes Hansen, Steve Pasterchick, Doug Loafman, Don Rutledge, Bobby Scheihing
    - Arbuckle Flat - Eric Taylor, 1976-11-30; wrc06568; 59229 (Box 6)
      Contents include: Eric Taylor playing live on the "Arbuckle Flat" radio program. Speakers: Eric Taylor, Trip Doss
    - State of the University, 1976-11; wrc06569; 59230 (Box 6)
      Contents include: Norman Hackerman takes questions from students. He discusses the university's decade long plan, the library's budget, faculty salaries, the role of the university president, over enrollment, funding for intramural sports and women's sports, admitting more out of state students, food services, the proctor's authority, support for clubs and organizations, the women's sports program, co-ed colleges, Resident Associates and Masters, and student apathy. Speakers: Norman Hackerman
    - Me & Paul live, part 1, 1976-12-02; wrc06570_01; 59234 (Box 6)
      Contents include: Me and Paul performing live in Willy's Pub. Speakers: James "Bubba" Hudson, Paul Rafferty
    - Me & Paul live, part 2, 1976-12-02; wrc06570_02; 59235 (Box 6)
    - Me & Paul live, part 3, 1976-12-02; wrc06570_03; 59210 (Box 6)
    - Rice Choral Christmas in the Chapel, 1976-12-02; wrc06573; 59237 (Box 6)
      Contents include: The Rice Chorale sings Christmas songs. Speakers: Rice Chorale
    - Promos and Reviews, Fall 1976; wrc06574; 59231 (Box 6)
      Contents include: (00:01) Rice Players' "Spoon River Anthology" review; (02:23) Wiess College's "Charlie's Aunt"; (05:18) "Lady Has No Heart" by St. Elmo's Fire; (10:06) "Let It Pour"; (12:54) "Come into My Own"; (17:54) Houston Symphony review; (21:21) Captain Lonely; (24:48) "Alice Doesn't Live Here Anymore" review; (27:51) St. Elmo's Fire concert promo; (29:39) "Pink Panther Strikes Again" review; (32:46) Sid Richardson College's "Dirty Work at the Crossroads" review; (35:12) "Dirty Work at the Crossroads" promo; (35:54) Billy Joel and Fever Tree concert review; (39:39) Blear's Weatherbeaten Paint; (41:05) Theme from "Bridge Over the River Kwai"; (43:49) Musical interlude; (44:18) Wind howling. Speakers: Stan Barber, John Gladu, Cullen Duke, James Aronovsky, Grungy
    - Ron Waters and Dan King, Fall 1976; wrc06575; 59194 (Box 6)
      Contents include: State Rep. Ron Waters and challenger Dan King discussed their political positions. There are problems with the audio. We deleted radio music at the beginning and ending of the recording. The recording was also too low with loud white noise, which we have removed. Speakers: Ron Waters, Dan King
    - News Master, Fall 1976; wrc06576 (Box 6)
      Contents include: (00:01) Rice Owls football vs. University of Texas preview; (02:37) College football; (04:12) Homer Rice on Rice Owls football; (0:58) Football stats and scoring; (05:28) Signal equipment upgraded; (05:59) College football; (07:09) Employees; (07:44) Gentle Art of Sports Betting; (09:28) Daily motivation for athletes; (09:58) Option play; (10:18) Football player on team; (10:53) Club sports; (11:33) Professional baseball, sports betting; (13:14) Football player on team; (13:57) Passing quarterback; (14:25) Homer Rice on SWC; (15:16) Mental health clinic; (16:41) Presidential vote, Dr. W.A. Criswell; (17:38) Course; (18:52) ASPCA animal euthanasia, pet education; (20:28) Walter Mondale and Bob Dole debate review; (23:27) Rice Owls football vs. Texas Tech review, college football; (24:21) Withholding tax skit; (25:29) Gentle Art of Sports Betting; (26:36) Journalists interviewing professors; (26:58) Homer Rice on coaching; (27:38) Student on football team; (28:09) College football; (29:13) Football player on team; (29:31) Homer Rice on team; (30:19) Liberal disillusionment survey; (31:31) Ron Paul question and answer session; (32:26) Gentle Art of Sports Betting; (33:57) Texans for Pres. Gerald Ford campaign; (35:33) Bob Gammage on government subsidizing of research; (36:38) Opponent of Bob Gammage; (37:15) Bob Gammage on opponent; (37:49) Political candidates visit Houston, Texas Democratic stronghold; (39:48) Jimmy Carter family on political polls, campaigning; (41:31) Jimmy Carter family campaigning; (42:20) Eugene McCarthy campaign and polls; (43:40) Convocation; (44:22) High school education; (44:52) Rosalynn Carter on mental health; (45:35) Texas Trails Association. Speakers: Dana Blankenhorn, Homer Rice, Tom Selman, Bill Wade, Bob Gammage, Lee Hochberg, Rosalynn Carter
    - News Master 3, 1976-1977; wrc06577; 59219 (Box 6)
      Contents include: (00:01) Gentle Art of Sports Betting; (02:02) Gentle Art of Sports Betting; (04:42) Gentle Art of Sports Betting; (06:23) Gentle Art of Sports Betting; (08:33) Tommy Kramer, football profits, student fans; (11:21) Southwest Conference games review; (12:18) Gentle Art of Sports Betting, traditions; (14:00) Rice Owls basketball vs. Waylon Baptist College review, college sports; (14:57) Gentle Art of Sports Betting, Heisman trophy, basketball; (16:06) Flu vaccine; (17:59) Hanszen carolers; (18:47) Pilot program languages; (19:35) Rice Owls Women's basketball; (20:10) Opinions; (20:26) Athlete critiquing Rice Owls basketball program, Bob Polk; (22:00) Athlete critiquing rats on basketball team; (22:12) Rice Owls basketball season review; (23:22) Thresher embezzlement case; (28:40) Stafford Stewart and others on the Thresher embezzlement case; (34:00) Student Association election results; (45:26) James M. Waters Creativity Award; (46:50) Texas re-ratification for Equal Rights Amendment. Speakers: Dana Blankenhorn, Peter Camp, Sam Carrington, Lee Hochberg, Stafford Stewart
    - Arbuckle Flat - Don Sanders, 1977-01-08; wrc06578; 59284 (Box 6)
      Contents include: Don Sanders playing live on the "Arbuckle Flat" radio program. He discusses his role in the Memorial Park oil drilling debate. Speaker: Don Sanders, Trip Doss
    - Up in the Air - HISD vs. WISD, 1977-01-13; wrc06579; 59253 (Box 6)
      Contents include: Larry Spencer, Loraine Burling [sp?], and Regan Sermons [sp?] discuss pros and cons of the proposal to create the Westheimer Independent School District, which would break away from the Houston Independent School District. We deleted radio music at the beginning of this recording. Speakers: Stan Barber, Larry Spencer, Hubert Holmes
    - Smokin' Fitz live, 1977-01-22; wrc06580; 59269 (Box 6)
      Contents include: Smokin' Fitz playing live. Location unknown. Speakers: Smokin' Fitz, Rock Romano
    - A Conversation with Jacques Cousteau, 1977-01-26; wrc06581; 59280 (Box 6)
      Contents include: Lee Hochberg and Patti Bellis interview Jacques Cousteau about his Involvement Day event in Houston at the Albert Thomas Convention Center. Speakers: Jacques Cousteau, Patti Bellis, Lee Hochberg, Liz Murphy, Alex Schmandt
    - Al Stewart live, 1977-01-27; wrc06582; 59258 (Box 6)
      Contents include: Al Stewart playing live. Location unknown. Speaker: Al Stewart